payperclicksearchengines.com 2019-01-10

# Privacy Policy - SpeedPPC

We won’t share or sell your information to any 3rd party including your email address. The information you provide us will only be used internally and will never be disclosed to parties other than SpeedPPC.

This privacy policy covers the site https://speedppc.com. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we disclose the following information.

  1. What personally identifiable information SpeedPPC collects.
  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
  3. What organization collects the information.
  4. How SpeedPPC uses the information.
  5. With whom SpeedPPC may share user information.
  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under SpeedPPC control.
  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

SpeedPPC is the sole owner of the infomation collected on our web site. SpeedPPC collects information at several different points on our Web site.

Information is collected for the purpose of matching the user with their account. Users have the option to participate in this activity for the purpose of enhancing your experience by customizing our site. A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last uri requested and browser type), interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image), computer information (computer and browser information), interactive data (account activity and searches performed), navigation and click-stream data (passive activity such as pages visited), computer information (computer and browser information), content (email content and bulletin board postings), demographic/socioeconomic data (characteristics such as gender), interactive data (account activity and searches performed), location data (current physical location), navigation and click-stream data (passive activity such as pages visited), online contact information (email address), preference data (what you like or dislike), unique identifiers (login id or other id), search terms (search text), transaction information (account transactions), user’s name, user’s birthdate, user’s login information, user’s gender (male or female), user’s home contact information and user’s business contact information. It is optional for the user to provide User’s Name, User’s Birthdate, User’s Gender (Male or Female), User’s Home Contact Information and User’s Business Contact Information. We encourage users to provide optional information so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. The reason we use this information is to complete the current transaction, contact by email or regular mail, enhance your experience by customizing our site, maintain and secure our site and understand (in aggregate) interests of website visitors. We retain this information as stated by our business practices. When users have data collected for the purposes of maintaining and securing our site and contacting by email or regular mail, they are given the opportunity to opt-out of information collected (Please see our Choice and Opt-out section).

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie. 

Our website uses cookies to enhance our site.

When customers provide us contact information for Website (users can opt-out by following the directions in our ‘Choice’ section) we use the information to contact the user to deliver sales and product information that will be useful to the them.

 **Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
Personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties.

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**  
Aggregate information is not shared with any third parties.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information.

When our web site originates email, users can opt-out of these communications by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email or by emailing us at contact@SpeedPPC.com.

**Data Security**  
SpeedPPC has some physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company uses secure encryption technology (secure socket connection) for all sensitive financial transmitted on our site.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes such as zip code, phone, email or postal address they can change online, physical contact, and other information. If a user wishes to correct/update information or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy.

**Links and Advertisements**  
Our website contains links to other sites. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We, SpeedPPC, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Changes to the Privacy Statement**  
The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. If we significantly change our policy, we will only apply the change to data collected after the change is made.

Using the following information, you can contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy via our contact form on the website.

If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, it can be resolved by contacting us using the details above.
